worldmarket.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy and Security | World Market

## World Market Privacy Policy

Effective date: October 2, 2017

World Market values your privacy. This notice details our privacy policy and practices so that you can have this information at your fingertips. We want you to know how we collect, use, and protect information about our customers. This privacy policy will tell you:

What information we collect  
What we do with the information we collect  
How we may share information  
How you can limit contact from us

We refer to World Market as the "Company," "we," "us" or "our." World Market's parent, Bed Bath & Beyond Inc., is also the parent company to the group of subsidiaries that operate retail store chains under the names Bed Bath & Beyond, Christmas Tree Shops And That!, Harmon and Harmon Face Values, buybuy BABY, One Kings Lane, PersonalizationMall.com, PMall, Of a Kind, Decorist, Chef Central and such other brands as we may acquire or launch from time to time, which we refer to collectively as, the "Brands".

By visiting our website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Our website may contain links to other websites operated and maintained by third parties. Other websites may also reference or link to our website. World Market is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. You should consult the individual privacy policies of those websites to determine their privacy practices before disclosing any information.

**Information We Collect**

**INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE**

We receive, and may store, any information you provide to us through our website. For example, we collect information that you provide when you place an order, register with us, send us an email, call us, sign up for our email offers or Rewards Program or enter a sweepstakes. This information may include:

your name;  
your mailing address;  
your billing address;  
your e-mail address;  
your phone number; and  
your credit card information.  

It may also include any other personal or preference information you provide to us, including a record of your online product purchases. It may also include information you submit about other people, for example, the name and address of a gift recipient. If you join our Rewards Program we will also store information about your purchases in order to calculate when you are eligible to receive a reward.

If you join our Rewards Program we will also store information about your purchases in order to calculate when you are eligible to receive a reward.

**AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED INFORMATION**

Our web servers automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us through our website. For example, when you visit the site, our system automatically recognizes your domain name and IP address(es), date and time of visits, the type of browser you use, the website from which your visit originated, page visits, time spent on web pages, and other similar traffic data. No personal information about you is revealed in this process. This information may be used by us to operate the website and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the website.

**COOKIES**

Our website uses "cookies" to customize your shopping experience or to keep track of your shopping cart. "Cookies" are pieces of information that are sent to your browser and stored in your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable us to more easily communicate and interact with you. You may disallow cookies through your web browser and still browse and shop on our website.

**INFORMATION FROM OTHER SOURCES**

We may obtain information about you from outside sources and combine it with your account information. For example, we may purchase commercially available demographics and other marketing information from third parties to help us better serve you or inform you about products or services that we think will be of interest to you.

We sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. Finally, we may also purchase lists containing your information (e.g., postal address, phone number, email address) for advertising and marketing purposes.

**Use Of Information**

**INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE**

We may use the information that you provide to us to process or follow up with transactions initiated on the website or through our customer service department, to let you know about products and promotions that we think may be of interest to you from us and the Brands, or to notify you when you have earned a reward under our Reward Program. We may share information provided by you directly or through cookies with companies that provide support services to us such as a transaction processor, printer, mailing house, or web host or with companies that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose, or to share that information with anyone other than the company and its agents.

**DISCLOSURE TO SUCCESSORS**

We may disclose information you provide to our website when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; when it is necessary to identify, contact, bring, or defend legal action against persons or entities that we believe may be causing harm to you, our company, or third parties; and when necessary, to protect or defend our rights or property.

**AGGREGATE INFORMATION**

We may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California law, you have the right to request and receive information from retailers concerning any third parties who have received information about you from the retailers for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Any such requests for information from us can be made by sending an email to privacy@cpwm.com or by calling us at 1-877-967-5362.

**Disclosures Ordered By Law**

We may disclose information you provide to our website when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; when it is necessary to identify, contact, bring, or defend legal action against persons or entities that we believe may be causing harm to you, our company, or third parties; and when necessary, to protect or defend our rights or property.

**Protecting Children's Privacy**

This is a general audience website; it is not directed at children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from any child under the age of 13 at this website, nor do we send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13.

**How You Can Limit Contact From Us**

**EMAILS**

If you provide our company with your email address, you may receive emails from us and the Brands. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional emails from us, please email us at emailunsubscribe@cpwm.com, or you may let us know by logging in to "My Profile" and indicating your preference. Please call 1-877-967-5362 if you have further questions about our email unsubscribe process. Your request will be handled promptly, although you may still receive marketing communications that were already in process prior to receipt of your request.

**OTHER MAILINGS**

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us that may include information on new products and services or upcoming events from us and the Brands. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at 1-877-967-5362. Your request will be handled promptly, although you may still receive marketing communications that were already in process prior to receipt of your request.

**CORRECTING OR UPDATING INFORMATION**

If you have registered with us, you may review for accuracy and update your profile information online by logging in to "My Profile" using your email address and password and editing your information accordingly. The length of time we keep your information will vary depending on the nature of your transactions on the website and information involved. We have retention standards that meet customer service, legal and regulatory needs. For these reasons, we may keep your information beyond the end of your relationship with us. When your information is no longer required, we will dispose of it with appropriate care and diligence.

**Security**

If you choose to create an account on our Site with a username and password, always exercise extreme care in protecting your password information and do not publicly share any of your passwords. You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of the Site by you or another person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you. Please notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security.

WE ENDEAVOR (AND REQUIRE OUR THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS TO ENDEAVOR) TO PROTECT THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US BY USING TECHNOLOGIES DESIGNED TO SECURE YOUR INFORMATION AS IT TRANSMITS TO US OVER THE INTERNET AND ONCE IT IS ON OUR SYSTEMS. BUT BECAUSE OF THE INHERENT NATURE OF THE INTERNET AS AN OPEN GLOBAL COMMUNICATIONS VEHICLE, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT SUCH INFORMATION STORED ON SERVERS SUPPORTING THIS SITE, TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM A USER, OR OTHERWISE IN OUR CARE (OR OUR THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS' CARE) WILL BE ABSOLUTELY SAFE FROM INTRUSION BY OTHERS, SUCH AS HACKERS. BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO ASSUME THESE RISKS.

**Updates To This Policy**

Updates and changes to this privacy policy will be posted on our website and will be effective from the date they are posted, unless otherwise noted. New policies will apply to all current and past users of the website and supersede any inconsistent policies previously in effect.

**Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this online privacy policy. This privacy policy is subject to change, so we encourage you to review it periodically.
